savenkeep.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy and Cookie Policy - Savenkeep

**Last update** : 30 March 2016  
**  
The protection of your privacy is one of our main objectives.  
** **(Privacy Act - Legislative Decree no. 196, 30 June 2003)**    
MOQU ADV Srl (hereinafter “MOQU”) undertakes to constantly protect the privacy on-line of its users. This document outlines our policy on privacy, explaining how your personal data are managed when using our services, and to enable you to give express consent to the processing of your personal data in the awareness of the sections in the website [Savenkeep.com](http://www.savenkeep.com/) (hereinafter: “Site”) requiring the entry of such data. The Site offers users third party information and materials in the form of links, banners, splash pages etc. (hereinafter: "Information"), to assist them in purchasing products and services on other web sites where the user may be redirected. By clicking on this information, users will directly access the site of the third parties, where they can complete their purchase of products and services and where the relative disclosure agreement is specifically governed in accordance with the data policy that the users find published directly on the site/s in question. In the same way, if the user decides to share the contents of the Site on social networks selectable via the key "share" provided, the relative privacy policy applicable to the sharing process will be governed in conformity with the data policy published on the social networks in question. The information you provide or otherwise acquired on registration for the various Site services will be subject to processing in compliance with the provisions of the Privacy Act (the full text of which can be found on the web site of the Italian Data Protection Authority [www.garanteprivacy.it](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/)), the Recommendations of the European Data Protection Authorities no. 2 of 17 May 2001 and the obligations for confidentiality that form the basis of the work of  MOQU. You can register for the Services by entering directly your name (or nickname), your e-mail address and password, or, if you have a Facebook profile or Google account, you can also register on the Site by clicking on the buttons "Access with Facebook" or “Access with Google”.   
In the latter case, the Site will automatically acquire your name, email address and avatar from Facebook or Google. The term "processing" refers to an operation or set of operations, also without the use of electronic devices, concerning the collection, recording, organization, storage, consultation, processing, modification, selection, extraction, comparison, use, interconnection, blocking, communication, dissemination, erasure and destruction of data, also when not recorded in a database.   
We also inform you that the personal data subject to processing may also constitute - depending also on your decision on how to use the Services - text information, photographic or video material, audio tracks, telephone utilities or any other information suitable for use as identification of the person concerned or identifiable depending on the type of Services requested. According to the provisions of the Privacy Act, the processes performed by MOQU will be based on the principles of fairness, legality and transparency and for the protection of your confidentiality and your rights.  
**  
Data Controller and Managers  
** The details of the Processing Controller are as follows: MOQU ADV Srl, with registered offices in in Via del Bosco Rinnovato 8, Milanofiori Nord, Assago (MI) - 20090, Building U4, Italy. The updated list of Processing Managers can be found at the registered offices of the Data Controller, and can be contacted for consultation at any time.

 **Purposes of processing  
** The data are processed for the purposes of provided the Services requested by the User. They will also be processed to comply with all legal, accounting and tax obligations. Personal data may also be processed for the purposes of enabling a user to browse and consult the Site. Note also that data are processed for the purpose of collection, conservation and processing of your data in order to conduct statistical analyses in anonymous and/or aggregate form, without the possibility of identifying the user as a person, aimed at monitoring the quality of services offered. Lastly, the optional, explicit and intentional delivery of emails to the addresses indicated on this Site will lead to the subsequent acquisition of the sender's address, required to send responses to requests, as well as any other personal data included in the message. Any specific and dedicated information will be progressively reported or displayed on the Site pages set up for specific services available on request.

 **Processing methods  
** Your personal data will be processed using automatic electronic instruments strictly for the time required to provide this service for which the data were collected. Special safety measures are implemented to prevent the loss of data, improper or incorrect use of the data or unauthorised access.

 **Communication and dissemination of common personal data  
** Your common personal data may be transferred to:    
1\. persons, companies or professional practices that provide assistance or consultancy services to MOQU on the subject of accounts, administration, legal, financial or tax matters, and for credit recovery in relation to the provision of the Services;   
2\. parties, entities or authorities entitled to receive your personal data as an obligation by law or on order from authorities;   
3\. parties, representatives and/or persons assigned by MOQU to perform activities strictly related to the provision of the Services and/or persons assigned and/or employed by MOQU to perform technical maintenance (including the maintenance of network apparatus and electronic communication networks), duly appointed, where necessary, as Data Managers in accordance with art. 29 of the Privacy Act, or Employees. With reference to the scope of disclosure of your personal data, the personal data required to activate the Services will not be subject to disclosure, with the exception of the nickname. In fact publication of the page that can be customised by the user is a necessary and integral element of the service offered by Save n' keep, and therefore both the user's nickname and the information openly entered in his/her page, will thus be made public and consequently subject to dissemination.

 **Optional or compulsory granting of consent  
** Apart from as specified below regarding browsing data and cookies, you are free to supply personal data stated in the form indicated in "contacts" to request the delivery of information or other data, and to register by entering your data in the registration window of the Site or by clicking on “Access with Facebook” or “Access with Google”. Failure to enter personal data may render impossible the activation of the requested Services.

 **Processing of personal data of third parties supplied by the person concerned  
** When using particular Services, some personal data of third parties may be processed if sent by you to the Service manager. In this case, you will be independently responsible for processing, with personal liability in accordance with the law. In this regard, you hence waiver, in the full sense of the term, the right to all disputes, claims, claims for damages due to processing etc., which may be submitted to the data controller of the said third party whose personal data have been processed through your use of the Services in breach of the application regulations on the protection of personal data. In any event, when you provide, in any form, parts of third party personal data when using the Service, you guarantee from this point - accepting all relevant liability - that this case of processing is based on prior acquisition - by yourself - of consent from the said third party to process the information that regards the latter.

 **Browsing data  
** The computer systems and software procedures used for operation of the web site acquire, during routine operation, some personal data, the transmission of which is considered implicit in the use of the Internet communication protocols. This information is not collected to be associated with identified persons, but which in their nature may, through processing and associations with data retained by third parties, enable the identification of users. This category of data includes IP addresses or domain names of the computer used by the users to connect to the site, URI (Uniform Resource Identifier) addresses of the requested resources, the time of the request, the method used to submit the request to the server, the dimensions of the file obtained in the response, the numerical code indicating the status of the response sent by the server (successful, error, etc.) and other parameters regarding the operating system and IT environment of the user. These data are used exclusively to retrieve anonymous statistical information on use of the site, and to ensure correct operation of the latter, and are deleted immediately after processing. The same data may be used to ascertain responsibility in the hypothetical case of computer crime harmful to the site or third parties: with the exception of this case, the data on web contacts are not stored permanently.   
**  
Cookies and their use   
** **When you visit this site with the browser set up to accept cookies, and you continue browsing (i.e. after closing the banner with "brief" information, you scroll through the page or click on an item) you automatically consent to the use of cookies by third parties to send profiled publicity and for statistical analyses.    
**Cookies are packets of information sent from a web server to the visitor/user's browser and memorised automatically on your device (personal computer, tablet, mobile phone, etc.), which are then re-sent automatically to the server each time you access the site. Cookies can only be used by the web server that sent them (or by any third parties with which they are originally shared); for example, this means that cookies generated by this site cannot be read by servers managed by third parties. The delivery of technical cookies by our servers is necessary to enable operation of some parts of the Service. Therefore, without these cookies, functionality of the site may be impaired or rendered impossible.   
This site also uses third party cookies. If you accept to receive cookies from third parties via this site, you can always change this option or disable it, according to the methods outlined below in this information section.   
You can also simply and quickly change settings of all or some cookies via the settings options in your browser (as described below).  
This section lists the types of cookies used and their purposes. 

_1\. Technical cookies used by the Owner  
_

 _2\. Third party cookies_  
This site also serves advertising and analytic cookies from third parties, as well as Social Network cookies. Note that these subjects, listed below with the relative links to their privacy policies, are independent owners of the data collection and handling processes via cookies; the user must therefore refer to their personal data handling policies (as specified in [FAQ no. 6 regarding cookies](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/web/guest/home/docweb/-/docweb-display/docweb/2142939) of the Italian Data Protection Authority).  
To disable cookies generated by advertisers, you can consult their specific privacy information or follow the instructions on the website of [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/). 

 _ **Apple Safari  
**_ Click on the menu 'Actions', select 'Preferences' in the main menu of the browser, select the tab 'Privacy' and then 'Details'.  
<https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265>

If this information is not sufficient, we recommend consulting the Help section of your browser for more details. On the other hand, if you wish to disable cookies generated by the advertisers, this can be done by following the instructions on the website of [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/).

**Art. 7 (Right of access to personal data and other rights)  
** You can contact the owner at any time to confirm the existence of your personal data and to see the contents and source, check accuracy or request integrations, updates or corrections (art. 7 of [Leg. Decree 196/03](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/) \- Italy).  
In accordance with the above article, you are also entitled to request cancellation, conversion to anonymous status or blocking of the data handled in breach of the law, as well as to dispute handing of this information, for legitimate reasons.  
 **  
Contacts    
**For any further information or to exert your rights as stated in [article 7 of Leg. Decree 196/2003](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/) (Italy) mentioned above please write to the email address displayed by the Captcha code viewed in the section “[Contacts](http://www.savenkeep.com/contact.html)” of the site, or send by fax to the number 055 20021550, stating your reasons for the request and attaching a copy of a valid ID document of the person concerned (legal representative in the case of a legal entity).

 _MOQU ADV Srl  
_ _Via del Bosco Rinnovato 8 -  _ _Milanofiori Nord  
Assago (MI), CAP 20090   
Building U4  
_ _Italy_

Note that only correctly formulated requests will be processed. ** **
